http://www.prostarsports.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy |
Rogers Athletic
ROGERS ATHLETIC CO.
PENDULUM
IMPACT ATHLETIC
Products
Our Brands
Rogers Athletic Co.
Our Brands
Rogers Athletic Co.
Our Brands
Rogers Athletic Co.
Contact
Get your practice and game day equipment fast with ROGERS 5-day Quickship
Update Cookie Settings
Update Cookie Settings
You're currently blocking cookies.
Rogers Privacy Policy
When you submit a form on our website we require information so that we can connect you with the appropriate representative and send you the proper information.
When you visit our website, your browser may send us information such as your web request, IP address, browser type. Cookies are used for measurement services, personalization, and targeted ads. The cookies allow us to provide you with targeted content when you’re on Facebook or other websites. The specific cookies used are below:
Cookie Name
Purpose
_RequestVerificationToken
This is an anti-forgery cookie set by web applications built using ASP.NET MVC technologies. It is designed to stop unauthorised posting of content to a website, known as Cross-Site Request Forgery. It holds no information about the user and is destroyed on closing the browser.
_cfduid
Used by CloudFare to identify trusted web traffic. It does not correspond to any user id nor does it store any peronally identifiable information.
_hssc
Used by HubSpot to determine if HubSpot should increment the session number and timestamps in the _hstc cookie. It contains the domain, viewCount, and session start timestamp.
_hssrc
Used by HubSpot whenever they change the session cookie. This cookie is also set to determine if the visitor has restarted their browser. If this cookie does not exist when HubSpot manages cookies, it is considered a new session.
_hstc
Used by HubSpot to track the domain, utk, initial timestamp, last timestamp, current timestamp, and session number.
hubspotutk
Used by HubSpot to keep track of a visitor's identity. It's passed to HubSpot on form submissions and used when deduplicating contacts.
_ga
Used by Google Analytics to track user activity over different browsing sessions.
_gid
Used by Google Analytics to distinguish users.
hblid
Cookie set by Olark Live Chat software. Identifies a unique visitor between visits
_ok
Cookie set by Olark Live Chat software, which provides functionality for websites to engage in instant messaging communication with visitors. Contains a site identifier, used for security purposes.
_okbk
Cookie set by Olark Live Chat software, which provides functionality for websites to engage in instant messaging communication with visitors. Contains sofware state information.
_okac
This cookie name is associated with live chat software provided by Olark that can be embedded in a website. It is used to help caching of interface elements to help with performance.
_okdetect
Used by Olark for live chat functionality.
_okgid
This cookie name is associated with the Olark Live Chat software product. It contains a group id for a site visitor.
_okla
Cookie associated with the Olark Live Chat software product. Used to help caching to improve performance.
_oklv
Cookie set by Olark Live Chat software, which provides functionality for websites to engage in instant messaging communication with visitors. Used to improve caching of software.
_vwo_uuid_v2
This cookie name is associated with the product Visual Website Optimiser, by USA based Wingify. The tool helps site owners measure the performance of different versions of web pages. This cookie ensures a visitor always sees the same version of a page and is used to track behaviour to measure the performance of different page versions.
ajs_anonymous_id
These cookies are generally used for Analytics and help count how many people visit a certain site by tracking if you have visited before. This cookie has a lifespan of 1 year.
ajs_group_id
These cookies track visitor usage and events within the website. Cookies in this domain have lifespan of 1 year.
ajs_user_id
This cookie helps track visitor usage, events, target marketing, and can also measure application performance and stability. Cookies in this domain have lifespan of 1 year.
amplitude_id_
Used by Olark Live Chat software and allows us to anonymously analyze how our website is interacted with so that we can make our customers’ experiences better.
amplitude_idundefinedolark.com
Used by Olark Live Chat software.
mdn_anonymous_id
Used by Olark Live Chat software to track device and session id.
merchello
This cookie helps with any merchandise purchase that you are making online.
olfsk
Cookie set by Olark Live Chat software. Maintains message history across pages.
wcsid
Cookie set by Olark Live Chat software. A session identifier used to keep track of a single chat session.
_gat
This cookie name is associated with Google Universal Analytics, according to documentation it is used to throttle the request rate - limiting the collection of data on high traffic sites. It expires after 10 minutes.
visitor_idaccountid
The visitor cookie includes a unique visitor ID and the unique identifier for your account. It is set by the Pardot tracking code.
visitor_id-hash
The visitor hash cookie contains the account ID and stores a unique hash. This cookie is a security measure to make sure that a malicious user can’t fake a visitor from Pardot and access corresponding prospect information.
pardot
A session cookie named pardot is set in your browser when you access a form, landing page, or page with Pardot tracking code. The cookie denotes an active session and isn’t used for tracking.
You do have the option to turn off cookies in your browser’s settings. Every browser is different, so look at your browser’s settings to determine how to make this change.
We do not sell your data with any third parties.
If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than what is in this privacy policy, we will offer you a way to opt-out.
Per the General Data Protection Regulation, citizens in the EU and EEA have the right to contact us to request any personal data we may have collected about them. They also have the right to have this data modified, restricted, or deleted.
3760 West Ludington Dr., Farwell, MI 48622
Ph: 800-457-5337
•
Fax: 888-549-9659
Customer service
3760 West Ludington Dr., Farwell, MI 48622
Ph: 800-457-5337
•
